[
    {
        "markdown":  "WyFbRG9jdW1lbnRhdGlvbl0oaHR0cHM6Ly9zaGllbGRzLmlvL2JhZGdlLy1Hb3RvX0RvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCldKGh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2VuLXVzL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvdGFrZW9wZXJhdG9yKQoKaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS90YWtlb3BlcmF0b3IKCioqKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqKioKClRoZSB0YWtlIG9wZXJhdG9yIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIG51bWJlciBvZiBzcGVjaWZpZWQgcm93cy4gVGhlIHJlc3VsdHMgYXJlIHRha2VuIGF0IHJhbmRvbSB1bmxlc3MgdGhlIHJvd3MgaGF2ZSBiZWVuIHNvcnRlZCBwcmlvciB0byB0aGUgdGFrZSBvcGVyYXRvciBiZWluZyBjYWxsZWQuCgoqKioqRXhhbXBsZToqKioqCgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgdGFrZSA1IDxicj4KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHRha2UgMTAKCioqKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKioqCgpUYWtlIGlzIGdyZWF0IHRvIHVzZSB3aGVuIGdyYWJiaW5nIHNhbXBsZSBzaXplIHJlc3VsdHMgZnJvbSBxdWVyaWVzLiBCeSBsb3dlcmluZyB0aGUgcmV0dXJuIG9mIHJvd3MgZnJvbSBhIHF1ZXJ5LCBxdWVyaWVzIHBlcmZvcm0gcXVpY2tlciB3aGVuIG5lZWRpbmcgYSBsb2cgcmVmZXJlbmNlLgo=",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Take",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "TakeEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return 1 row from the Weather table in the default order",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlciB8IGxpbWl0IDE="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "TakeEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return 6 rows from the Weather table in the default order",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlciB8IHRha2UgNg=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "TakeEx3",
                                            "question":  "Return 10 rows from the Weather table in the default order",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlciB8IHRha2UgMTA="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  3
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "WyFbRG9jdW1lbnRhdGlvbl0oaHR0cHM6Ly9zaGllbGRzLmlvL2JhZGdlLy1Eb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uLWluZm9ybWF0aW9uYWwpXSggaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS93aGVyZW9wZXJhdG9yKQoKaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS93aGVyZW9wZXJhdG9yCgoqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioKPHA+ClRoZSB3aGVyZSBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB0aGUgbW9zdCBjb21tb25seSB1c2VkIG9wZXJhdG9yIHdpdGhpbiBLUUwuIFRoZSB3aGVyZSBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB1c2VkIHdpdGhpbiBhbG1vc3QgZXZlcnkgS3VzdG8gcXVlcnkuIFRoZSB3aGVyZSBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB1c2VkIGZvciBmaWx0ZXJpbmcgcmVzdWx0cyBiYXNlZCBvbiBzcGVjaWZpZWQgY3JpdGVyaWEuIFRoaXMgb3BlcmF0b3IgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgd2l0aCBtYW55IG90aGVyIG9wZXJhdG9ycywgc3VjaCBhcyBlcXVhbGl0eSBvcGVyYXRvcnMsIHN0cmluZyBvcGVyYXRvcnMsIHRpbWUgYmFzZWQgb3BlcmF0b3JzLCBhbmQgbW9yZS4KPC9wPgoKKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGNvdW50KCkgYnkgUHJvdmlkZXJOYW1lIHwgd2hlcmUgY291bnRfIDwgMTAwIDwvYnI+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBDb21wdXRlciBjb250YWlucyAnZGVza3RvcCcgPC9icj4KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPCBhZ28oMWgpIDxici8+CjwvcD4KCioqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioKPHA+CldoZXJlIHNob3VsZCBiZSB1c2VkIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBhcHBseSBmaWx0ZXJpbmcgY3JpdGVyaWEuIFdoZXJlIGlzIHRoZSBzaW1wbGVzdCBmb3JtIGZvciBmaWx0ZXJpbmcgYW5kIGFzIG1lbnRpb25lZCBjYW4gYmUgZ3JvdXBlZCB3aXRoIG90aGVyIG9wZXJhdG9ycyB0byBmdXJ0aGVyIGltcHJvdmUgdGhlIGxvZyByZXN1bHRzLgo8L3A+Cg==",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Where",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "WhereEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return all rows where the \u0027location\u0027 is houston",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uID09ICJIb3VzdG9uIg=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "WhereEx2",
                                            "question":  "From the Weather table, return all lows and highs above 71",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlciB8wqB3aGVyZcKgTG93wqA+wqA3McKgYW5kwqBIaWdowqA+wqA3MQ=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "WhereEx3",
                                            "question":  "Return the newest row from Philadelphia in the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uID09ICJQaGlsYWRlbHBoaWEiCnwgdGFrZSAx"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "WhereEx4",
                                            "question":  "Return the oldest row from Seattle in the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uID09ICJTZWF0dGxlIgp8IHNvcnQgYnkgVGltZUdlbmVyYXRlZCBhc2MKfCB0YWtlIDE="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvc3VtbWFyaXplb3BlcmF0b3IKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIHN1bW1hcml6ZSBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB1c2VkIHRvIGFnZ3JlZ2F0ZSB0aGUgY29udGVudCBvZiBhIHRhYmxlIGJhc2VkIG9uIHRoZSBsaXN0ZWQgY29sdW1uIG9yIGNvbHVtbnMuIFRoaXMgaXMgbW9zdCB1c2VmdWwgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIGN1dCBkb3duIG9uIHRoZSByZXN1bHRzIHNob3duIHdoaWxlIHN1bW1hcml6aW5nIHRoZSBjb2x1bW5zIG9mIGludGVyZXN0LiBTdW1tYXJpemUgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgYnkgaXRzZWxmIG9yIHdpdGggb3RoZXIgYWdncmVnYXRlcnMgc3VjaCBhcyBjb3VudCgpLCBhcmdfbWF4KCksIGFyZ19taW4oKSwgb3IgYXZnKCkuIFVzaW5nIG11bHRpcGxlIGNvbHVtbnMgYWxsb3dzIGZvciBzdHJvbmdlciBjb21iaW5hdGlvbnMgd2l0aGluIHRoZSByZXN1bHRzLgo8L3A+CgogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGNvdW50KCkgYnkgUHJvdmlkZXJOYW1lIHwgd2hlcmUgY291bnRfIDwgMTAwIDwvYnI+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgYnkgQ29tcHV0ZXIsIEV2ZW50SUQgPC9icj4KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPCBhZ28oMWgpIHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGJ5IEFjY291bnQgPGJyLz4KPC9wPgoKICoqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioKPHA+ClN1bW1hcml6ZSBzaG91bGQgYmUgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGFnZ3JlZ2F0aW5nIGRhdGEgd2l0aGluIGxvZ3MgYmFzZWQgb24gcmVsYXRpb24gb3IgaW50ZXJlc3QuIEZvciBleGFtcGxlLCBzdW1tYXJpemluZyB3aGljaCBldmVudHMgYXJlIHJlcG9ydGluZyBmb3IgZGV2aWNlLiBTdW1tYXJpemUgY2FuIGFsc28gYmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgdGltZS1zZXJpZXMgYW5hbHlzaXMgYnkgZ2VuZXJhdGluZyB0aGUgY291bnQgb2YgZXZlbnRzIGJ5IHRvcGljIG92ZXIgYSBzcGVjaWZpZWQgdGltZSByYW5nZS4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Summarize",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the count of each temperature has shown up for Seattle",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uID09ICdTZWF0dGxlJwp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBjb3VudCgpIGJ5IExvdywgSGlnaA=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return the number of times that New York was over 85 degrees",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uID09ICdOZXcgWW9yayBDaXR5Jwp8IHdoZXJlIEhpZ2ggPiA4NQp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBjb3VudCgp"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx3",
                                            "question":  "Return the number of distinct High temperatures found in the Weather table \u003cbr\u003e\u003cbr\u003e You will need to use `dcount()`. ```T | summarize dcount(V) by G | count```",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnQoSGlnaCk="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx4",
                                            "question":  "Return the number of rows with rainfall in the Weather table and the total rainfall accumulation",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnQoUmFpbiksIHN1bShSYWluKQ=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx5",
                                            "question":  "Return a summary of Locations from the Weather table in descending order of Location",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBieSBMb2NhdGlvbgp8IHNvcnQgYnkgTG9jYXRpb24gZGVzYw=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SummarizeEx6",
                                            "question":  "Return a summary of the total number of rows with rainfall",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIFJhaW4gPiAwCnwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGNvdW50KCk="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  5
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvcHJvamVjdG9wZXJhdG9yCjwvcD4KCiAqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioKPHA+ClRoZSBwcm9qZWN0IG9wZXJhdG9yIHJldHVybnMgb25seSB0aGUgY29sdW1ucyBzcGVjaWZpZWQgaW4gdGhlIHF1ZXJ5LiBUaGlzIG9wZXJhdG9yIGlzIHVzZWZ1bCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gdHJpbSByZXN1bHRzIHRvIG9ubHkgcmV0dXJuIHRoZSBjb2x1bW5zIGFuZCBjb250ZW50IG9mIHZhbHVlIG9yIGludGVyZXN0LiBQcm9qZWN0IGNhbiBhbHNvIHJlbmFtZSBjb2x1bW5zIHdoZW4gcmV0dXJuaW5nIHRoZW0uCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5QWxlcnQgfCBwcm9qZWN0IFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQsIEFsZXJ0TmFtZSwgUHJvdmlkZXJOYW1lLCBFbnRpdGllcyA8L2JyPgpTZWN1cml0eUV2ZW50IHwgd2hlcmUgRXZlbnRJRCA9PSA0NjI0IHwgcHJvamVjdCBDb21wdXRlciwgVXNlciwgQWN0aW9uUGVyZm9ybWVkPVByb2Nlc3MgPC9icj4KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPCBhZ28oMWgpIHwgcHJvamVjdCBBY2NvdW50LCBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkLCBSZXN1bHQgPGJyLz4KPC9wPgoKICoqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioKPHA+ClByb2plY3Qgc2hvdWxkIGJlIHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW4gdG8gZWxpbWluYXRlIHVubmVlZGVkIGNvbHVtbnMgZnJvbSByZXN1bHRzLiBUaGlzIHdpbGwgbWFrZSB0aGUgcmVzdWx0cyBtb3JlIHBlcnNvbmFsaXplZCBidXQgYWxzbyB3aWxsIGluY3JlYXNlIHF1ZXJ5IHBlcmZvcm1hbmNlLiBXaGVuIHJlbmFtaW5nIGNvbHVtbnMsIHRoaXMgaXMgdXNlZnVsIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byByZW5hbWUgY29sdW1ucyB3aGVuIG5vcm1hbGl6aW5nIGRhdGEgb3IgcGVyZm9ybWluZyBqb2lucyBhcyB0aGUgY29sdW1ucyBjYW4gdGhlbiBzaGFyZSBhIGNvbW1vbiBjb2x1bW4gdGl0bGUgaWYgdGhhdCBpcyBub3QgYWxyZWFkeSB0aGUgY2FzZS4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Project",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ProjectEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return High temperatures of all records from the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHByb2plY3QgSGlnaA=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ProjectEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return High and Low temperatures of all records from the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHByb2plY3QgSGlnaCwgTG93"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ProjectEx3",
                                            "question":  "Rename the Low column to LowestTemperature and return the results",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHByb2plY3QgTG93ZXN0VGVtcGVyYXR1cmUgPSBMb3c="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9wcm9qZWN0YXdheW9wZXJhdG9yDQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioNCjxwPg0KVGhlIHByb2plY3QtYXdheSBvcGVyYXRvciBkb2VzIGEgc2ltaWxhciBmdW5jdGlvbiBhcyBwcm9qZWN0LiBQcm9qZWN0LWF3YXkgcmVtb3ZlcyB0aGUgdW53YW50ZWQgY29sdW1ucyBmcm9tIHRoZSBmdWxsIGxpc3Qgb2YgY29sdW1ucyBpbiB0aGUgcmVzdWx0cy4NCjwvcD4NCg0KICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKg0KPHA+DQpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgcHJvamVjdC1hd2F5IFByb2Nlc3NpbmdFbmRUaW1lLCBUeXBlIDwvYnI+DQpTZWN1cml0eUV2ZW50IHwgd2hlcmUgRXZlbnRJRCA9PSA0NjI0IHwgcHJvamVjdC1hd2F5IFNvdXJjZUNvbXB1dGVySUQsIE1HLCBNYW5kYXRvcnlMYWJlbCA8L2JyPg0KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPCBhZ28oMWgpIHwgcHJvamVjdC1hd2F5IExldmVsLCBQcm9jZXNzaW5nVGltZUluTWlsbGlzZWNvbmRzIDxici8+DQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqDQo8cD4NClByb2plY3QtYXdheSBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBtb3N0IGNvbHVtbnMgc2hvdWxkIHJlbWFpbiBleGNlcHQgZm9yIGEgc2VsZWN0IGZldy4gSXQgaXMgZWFzaWVyIHRvIHVzZSBwcm9qZWN0LWF3YXkgdG8gcmVtb3ZlIHRoZSBmZXcgY29sdW1ucyByYXRoZXIgdGhhbiB1c2luZyBwcm9qZWN0IHRvIHJlY3JlYXRlIHRoZSBsaXN0IG9mIGNvbHVtbnMgdG8gcHJlc2VudCBpbiB0aGUgcmVzdWx0cy4NCjwvcD4NCg==",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "ProjectAway",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ProjectAwayEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return all records excluding the High column from the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHByb2plY3QtYXdheSBIaWdo"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ProjectAwayEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return all records excluding the High and Rain columns from the Weather table",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHByb2plY3QtYXdheSBIaWdoLCBSYWlu"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9kYXRhdHlwZXMtc3RyaW5nLW9wZXJhdG9ycw0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSBjb250YWlucyBvcGVyYXRvciB0YWtlcyBhIHN0cmluZyBhbmQgZmlsdGVycyB0aGUgbG9ncyBiYXNlZCBvbiB0aGUgc3RyaW5nLiBDb250YWlucyBpcyBub3QgY2FzZSBzZW5zaXRpdmUuDQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioNCjxwPg0KU2VjdXJpdHlBbGVydCB8IHdoZXJlIFByb3ZpZGVyTmFtZSBjb250YWlucyAnbTM2NSBkZWZlbmRlcicgPC9icj4NClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBFdmVudElEID09IDQ2MjQgfCB3aGVyZSBDb21wdXRlciBjb250YWlucyAnZGMwMScgPC9icj4NClNpZ25pbkxvZ3MgfCB3aGVyZSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkIDwgYWdvKDFoKSB8IHdoZXJlIEFjY291bnQgY29udGFpbnMgJ2FkbWluJyA8YnIvPg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKg0KPHA+DQpDb250YWlucyBjYW4gYmUgdXNlZCBpbiBwbGFjZSBvZiB0aGUgdXN1YWwgJz09JyBzdHJpbmcgY29tcGFyaXNvbiBmaWx0ZXIgd2hpbGUgcHJvdmlkaW5nIHJlbGF4ZWQgY2FzZSBzZW5zaXRpdml0eS4gVGhpcyBjYW4gYmUgdXNlZnVsIHdoZW4gcGVyZm9ybWluZyBzZWFyY2hlcyBhbmQgZmlsdGVyaW5nIG9mIGxvZ3Mgb24gYW4gaXRlbSB3aGVyZSBjYXBpdGFsaXphdGlvbiBpcyB1bmtub3duLg0KPC9wPg0K",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Contains",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ContainsEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return records from the Weather table with Location values that have the letter \"s\" in them",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvY2F0aW9uIGNvbnRhaW5zICdzJw=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9kYXRhdHlwZXMtc3RyaW5nLW9wZXJhdG9ycw0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClNpbWlsYXIgdG8gdGhlIGNvbnRhaW5zIG9wZXJhdG9yLCB0aGUgaGFzIG9wZXJhdG9yIHRha2VzIGEgc3RyaW5nIGFuZCBmaWx0ZXJzIHRoZSBsb2dzIGJhc2VkIG9uIHRoZSBzdHJpbmcuIENvbnRhaW5zIGlzIG5vdCBjYXNlIHNlbnNpdGl2ZS4NCjwvcD4NCg0KICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKg0KPHA+DQpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgd2hlcmUgUHJvdmlkZXJOYW1lIGhhcyAnbTM2NSBkZWZlbmRlcicgPC9icj4NClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBFdmVudElEID09IDQ2MjQgfCB3aGVyZSBDb21wdXRlciBoYXMgJ2RjMDEnIDwvYnI+DQpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgd2hlcmUgVGltZUdlbmVyYXRlZCA8IGFnbygxaCkgfCB3aGVyZSBBY2NvdW50IGhhcyAnYWRtaW4nIDxici8+DQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqDQo8cD4NCkhhcyBwZXJmb3JtcyB0aGUgc2FtZSBmdW5jdGlvbmFsaXR5IGFzIENvbnRhaW5zIGJ1dCBwcm92aWRlcyBiZXR0ZXIgcGVyZm9ybWFuY2Ugd2hlbiBydW5uaW5nIHRoZSBxdWVyeS4NCjwvcD4NCg==",
        "tab":  "Overview",
        "section":  "Has",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "HasEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return all records from the Mordor table that have the word \"cleared\" in the Message column",
                                            "dataset":  "Mordor",
                                            "answer":  "TW9yZG9yIHwgd2hlcmUgTWVzc2FnZSBoYXMgJ2NsZWFyZWQn"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9hZ29mdW5jdGlvbg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSBhZ28gb3BlcmF0b3IgdGFrZXMgdGhlIGN1cnJlbnQgdGltZSBhbmQgc3VidHJhY3RzIHRoZSBzcGVjaWZpZWQgYW1vdW50IG9mIHRpbWUgZnJvbSBpdC4gVGhlIHRpbWUgc3VidHJhY3RlZCBjYW4gYmUgZG9uZSBpbiBzZWNvbmRzIChzKSwgbWludXRlcyAobSksIGhvdXJzIChoKSwgYW5kIGRheXMgKGQpLg0KDQphZ28gc2hvdWxkIGJlIHVzZWQgYWZ0ZXIgdXNpbmcgZXF1YWxpdHkgb3BlcmF0b3JzIHN1Y2ggYXMgPiwgPCwgPj0sIDw9Lg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqDQo8cD4NClNlY3VyaXR5QWxlcnQgfCB3aGVyZSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkID49IGFnbygyZCkgfCB3aGVyZSBQcm92aWRlck5hbWUgaGFzICdtMzY1IGRlZmVuZGVyJyA8L2JyPg0KU2VjdXJpdHlFdmVudCB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPCBhZ28gKDFoKXwgd2hlcmUgRXZlbnRJRCA9PSA0NjI0IHwgd2hlcmUgQ29tcHV0ZXIgaGFzICdkYzAxJyA8L2JyPg0KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPD0gYWdvKDMwbSkgfCB3aGVyZSBBY2NvdW50IGhhcyAnYWRtaW4nIDxici8+DQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqDQo8cD4NCmFnbyBzaG91bGQgYWx3YXlzIGJlIHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIGZpbHRlciBkYXRhIHRvIGJlIHdpdGhpbiBhIGNlcnRhaW4gdGltZSB3aW5kb3cuID49IG9yIDw9IHNob3VsZCBiZSB1c2VkIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byByZXR1cm4gZGF0YSBvdXRzaWRlIG9mIG9yIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgdGltZSByYW5nZS4NCjwvcD4NCg==",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Ago",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "AgoEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return all \u0027userlogins\u0027 table records from the last 7 days",
                                            "dataset":  "userlogins",
                                            "answer":  "dXNlcmxvZ2lucwp8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPiBhZ28oN2Qp"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "AgoEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return all \u0027userlogins\u0027 table records from more than 30 days ago",
                                            "dataset":  "userlogins",
                                            "answer":  "dXNlcmxvZ2lucwp8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgPiBhZ28oMzBkKQ=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvYmV0d2Vlbm9wZXJhdG9yCjwvcD4KCiAqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioKPHA+ClRoZSBiZXR3ZWVuIG9wZXJhdG9yIG1hdGNoZXMgdGhlIGlucHV0IHRoYXQgaXMgaW5zaWRlIHRoZSBpbmNsdXNpdmUgcmFuZ2UuIFRoaXMgY2FuIGJlIGJldHdlZW4gaW50ZWdlcnMgb3IgZGF0ZXRpbWUgaXRlbXMuCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5QWxlcnQgfCB3aGVyZSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkIGJldHdlZW4gKG5vdyAuLiBhZ28oOGQpKSB8IHdoZXJlIFByb3ZpZGVyTmFtZSBoYXMgJ20zNjUgZGVmZW5kZXInIDwvYnI+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkIDwgYWdvICgxaCl8IHdoZXJlIEV2ZW50SUQgYmV0d2VlbiAoNDAwMCAuLiA1MDAwKSB8IHdoZXJlIENvbXB1dGVyIGhhcyAnZGMwMScgPC9icj4KU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgYmV0d2VlbiAoZGF0ZXRpbWUoMjAyMS0wMS0wMSAwMDowMDowMCkgLi4gZGF0ZXRpbWUoMjAyMS0wMi0wMSAwMDowMDowMCkpIHwgd2hlcmUgQWNjb3VudCBoYXMgJ2FkbWluJyA8YnIvPgo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KYmV0d2VlbiBpcyBhIHN0cm9uZyBvcGVyYXRvciB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgZm9yIGRhdGEgd2l0aGluIGEgdGltZSByYW5nZSBvciBudW1lcmljYWwgcmFuZ2UuIEZvciB0aW1lIHJhbmdlcywgaXQgY2FuIHJldHVybiBkYXRhIGdlbmVyYXRlZCBiZXR3ZWVuIHR3byBvciBtb3JlIG1vbnRocyB3aXRob3V0IGhhdmluZyB0byBjb21wYXJlIHRoZSB0aW1lIHRvIHRoZSBjdXJyZW50IHRpbWUuIEZvciBudW1iZXIgcmFuZ2VzLCB0aGlzIGNhbiBiZSB1c2VkIGluIHBsYWNlIG9mIGEgPCA+IGNvbXBhcmlzb24gZm9yIHJhbmdlcy4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Between",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "BetweenEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return rows from the Weather table with a Low between 20 and 22",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIExvdyBiZXR3ZWVuICgyMCAuLiAyMik="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "BetweenEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return rows from the Weather table with Rain between 0.8 and 1",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIFJhaW4gYmV0d2VlbiAoMC44IC4uIDEp"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "BetweenEx3",
                                            "question":  "Return all rows where the time is between 2015-06-25 and 2015-06-30",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQgYmV0d2VlbihkYXRldGltZSgiMjAxNS0wNi0yNSIpIC4uIGRhdGV0aW1lKCIyMDE1LTA2LTI5Iikp"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  3
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvY2FzZWZ1bmN0aW9uCjwvcD4KCiAqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioKPHA+ClRoZSBjYXNlIG9wZXJhdG9yIGV2YWx1YXRlcyBhIGxpc3Qgb2YgaXRlbXMgYW5kIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IHJlc3VsdCB3aGVuIHRoZSBpdGVtIGlzIHNhdGlzZmllZC4gSWYgbm9uZSBvZiB0aGUgaXRlbXMgYXJlIHRydWUsIHRoZSByZXN1bHQgb2YgdGhlIGxhc3QgaXRlbSBpcyByZXR1cm5lZC4gQ2FzZSBjYW4gYmUgc2VlbiBhcyBhIGxpc3Qgb2YgaWYvZWxzZSBzdGF0ZW1lbnRzIHRoYXQgcnVucyBhIGNoZWNrIG9uIGVhY2ggaXRlbSB0byBzZWUgaWYgdGhleSBhcmUgdHJ1ZS4gSWYgbm90LCByZXR1cm4gdGhlIGRlZmF1bHQgZWxzZSB2YWx1ZS4KPC9wPgoKICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKgo8cD4KVGFibGUgfCBleHRlbmQgVmFyaWFibGUgPSBjYXNlKCBTaXplIDw9IDMsICJTbWFsbCIsIFNpemUgPD0gMTAsICJNZWRpdW0iLCAiTGFyZ2UiKSA8L2JyPgpTZWN1cml0eUV2ZW50IHwgZXh0ZW5kIENhdGVnb3J5ID0gY2FzZShFdmVudElEIGJldHdlZW4gKDQ2MjAgLi4gNDYzMCksICJBdXRoZW50aWNhdGlvbiIsIEV2ZW50SUQgYmV0d2VlbiAoNDcyMCAuLiA0NzMwKSwgIkFjY291bnQgYmFzZWQiLCAiVW5jbGFzc2lmaWVkIikgfCBwcm9qZWN0IEV2ZW50SUQsIENhdGVnb3J5ICA8L2JyPgo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KQ2FzZSBzaG91bGQgYmUgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gdGFnIG9yIGNsYXNzaWZ5IGRhdGEgYmFzZWQgb24gZmlsdGVycy4gVGhlIHJldHVybiB2YWx1ZSBmb3IgZWFjaCBjYXNlIGNhbiBiZSBhIHN0YXRpYyBzdHJpbmcgb3IgYSBkeWFubWljIHZhbHVlIGZyb20gYSBjb2x1bW4vdmFyaWFibGUuIFRoaXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgdG8gZmlsdGVyIG91dCBvbmx5IHJlbHZhbnQgY29sdW1ucyB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gcGVyZm9ybSBjYXNlIG1hdGNoaW5nLgo8L3A+Cg==",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Case",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "CaseEx1",
                                            "question":  "Extend a Feeling column that lists \"hot\" for High over 80, \"warm\" for High over 65, and \"cool\" for other Highs",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IGV4dGVuZCBGZWVsaW5nID0gY2FzZSAoSGlnaCA+IDgwLCAiaG90IiwgSGlnaCA+IDY1LCAid2FybSIsICJjb29sIik="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9zY2FsYXItZGF0YS10eXBlcy9kYXRldGltZQ0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSBkYXRldGltZSBvcGVyYXRvciByZXByZXNlbnRzIGFuIGluc3RhbnQgaW4gdGltZSwgdHlwaWNhbGx5IGV4cHJlc3NlZCBhcyBhIGRhdGUgYW5kIHRpbWUgb2YgZGF5LiBWYWx1ZXMgcmFuZ2UgaW4gMDA6MDA6MDAgKG1pZG5pZ2h0KSB0aHJvdWdoIDExOjU5OjU5IFBNLg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqDQo8cD4NClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkIGJldHdlZW4gKGRhdGV0aW1lKDIwMjEtMDEtMDEgMDE6NDU6MDApLi5kYXRldGltZSgyMDIxLTAxLTMxIDExOjAwOjAwKSkgIDwvYnI+DQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqDQo8cD4NCkRhdGV0aW1lIHNob3VsZCBiZSB1c2VkIHdoZW4gdXNpbmcgdGhlIGJldHdlZW4gb3BlcmF0b3Igb3Igd2hlbiBjcmVhdGluZyBhIGRhdGF0YWJsZS4gRGF0ZXRpbWUgd2lsbCBoZWxwIHRoZSBxdWVyeSByZW5kZXIgYSBkYXRlIHRoYXQgaXMgYSBzdHJpbmcgYW5kIHNwZWNpZnkgaWYgYSBjb2x1bW4gaXMgYSBkYXRlLg0KPC9wPg0K",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Datetime",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "DatetimeEx1",
                                            "question":  "Print the time difference between midnight UTC January 22nd 2014 and 3pm UTC on October 1st 2000",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvaWZmZnVuY3Rpb24KPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIGlmZiBvcGVyYXRvciBldmFsdWF0ZXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IGFyZ3VtZW50IGFuZCByZXR1cm5zIHRoZSB2YWx1ZSBvZiBlaXRoZXIgdGhlIHNlY29uZCBvciBsYXN0IGFyZ3VtZW50IGRlcGVuZGluZyBvbiB3aGljaCBpdGVtIGlzIHRydWUuIElmIHRydWUsIHRoZSBzZWNvbmQgb3B0aW9uIGlzIHJldHVybmVkLiBJZiBmYWxzZSwgdGhlIHRoaXJkIG9wdGlvbiBpcyByZXR1cm5lZC4gSWZmIG11c3QgYmUgdXNlZCB3aXRoIHRoZSBleHRlbmQgb3BlcmF0b3IgdG8gY3JlYXRlIGEgdmFyaWFibGUgdGhhdCB3aWxsIHRha2Ugb24gdGhlIHZhbHVlIHJldHVybmVkIGZyb20gdGhlIGlmZiBzdGF0ZW1lbnQuCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5SW5jaWRlbnQgfCBleHRlbmQgaWZmKGlzZW1wdHkoT3duZXIpID09IHRydWUsICJUaGlzIGluY2lkZW50IGlzIG5vdCBvd25lZC4iLCBPd25lcikgIDwvYnI+CgpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgZXh0ZW5kIEJyb3dzZXJDaGVjayA9IGlmZihEZXZpY2VEZXRhaWwuYnJvd3NlciAhaGFzICdFZGdlJywgIlVzZXIgaXMgYnJlYWtpbmcgcG9saWN5IGJ5IHVzaW5nIHVuc3VwcG9ydGVkIHdlYiBicm93c2Vycy4iLCAiQnJvd3NlciBjb21wbGlhbnQgZm9yIHRoaXMgYXV0aGVudGljYXRpb24uIikgIDwvYnI+CjwvcD4KCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqCjxwPgppZmYgaXMgYmVzdCB1c2VkIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBzZXQgYm9vbGVhbiBjaGVja3Mgb3IgcnVuIGNoZWNrcyB0aGF0IHdpbGwgbGV2ZXJhZ2UgcmVzdWx0cyBkZXNpcmVkIGlmIHRydWUgb3IgaWYgZmFsc2UuIElmZiBpcyBhIGdyZWF0IHJlcGxhY2VtZW50IGZvciBjYXNlIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBwZXJmb3JtIHNob3J0IGNoZWNrcyByYXRoZXIgdGhhbiBzZXZlcmFsLgo8L3A+Cg==",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Iff",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "IffEx1",
                                            "question":  "Extend a new column that will check if its raining or not based on the Rain value is greater than 0.",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IGV4dGVuZCBpc3JhaW5pbmcgPSBpZmYoUmFpbiA+IDAsICJyYWluaW5nIiwgIm5vdCByYWluaW5nIik="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9zb3J0b3BlcmF0b3INCg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSBzb3J0IG9wZXJhdG9yIHNvcnRzIHRoZSByb3dzIG9mIHRoZSBpbnB1dCB0YWJsZSBpbiBvcmRlciBieSBvbmUgb3IgbW9yZSBjb2x1bW5zLiBBc2MgKWFzY2VuZGluZykgYW5kIGRlc2MgKGRlc2NlbmRpbmcpIGFyZSB1c2VkIHRvIGRpY3RhdGUgd2hpY2ggc29ydGluZyBtZXRob2QgaXMgdXNlZC4NCjwvcD4NCg0KICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKg0KPHA+DQpTZWN1cml0eUV2ZW50IHwgcHJvamVjdCBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkLCBDb21wdXRlciwgVXNlciB8IHNvcnQgYnkgQ29tcHV0ZXIgYXNjICA8L2JyPg0KDQpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgcHJvamVjdCBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkLCBBY2NvdW50IHwgc29ydCBieSBUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkIGFzYyA8L2JyPg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKg0KPHA+DQpzb3J0IGlzIGJlc3QgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gc3VyZmFjZSBjZXJ0YWluIHJlc3VsdHMgZmlyc3QgaW4gdGhlIGxpc3QuIFNvcnQgY2FuIGFwcGx5IHRvIGFueSByZXR1cm5lZCBjb2x1bW4gaW4gb3JkZXIgdG8gb3JnYW5pemUgdGhlIHJlc3VsdHMuIA0KPC9wPg0K",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "Sort",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "SortEx1",
                                            "question":  "Sort Weather results by amount of Rain from most to least",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHNvcnQgYnkgUmFpbiBkZXNj"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "RG9jdW1lbnRhdGlvbjogaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9wYXJzZWpzb25mdW5jdGlvblx1MDAzY2JyL1x1MDAzZVx1MDAzY2JyL1x1MDAzZQ0KDQpUaGUgdG9keW5hbWljKCkgb3BlcmF0b3IgaW50ZXJwcmV0cyBhIHN0cmluZyBhcyBhIEpTT04gdmFsdWUgYW5kIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIHZhbHVlIGFzIGR5bmFtaWMuIFdvcmtzIHNpbWlsaWxhcmx5IGFzIHRoZSBwYXJzZV9qc29uIG9wZXJhdG9yLg0KDQpFeGFtcGxlOg0KZXh0ZW5kIFZhcmlhYmxlID0gcGFyc2VfanNvbihuZXN0ZWRKc29uSXRlbSksIGV4dGVuZCBWYXJpYWJsZSA9IHRvZHluYW1pYyhuZXN0ZWRKc29uSXRlbSlcdTAwM2Nici9cdTAwM2U=",
        "tab":  "Scalar",
        "section":  "ToDynamic",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ToDynamicEx1",
                                            "question":  "Convert WinEvents from the table \u0027Events\u0027 to dynamic. Extend a new column called EventID and reference the EventID from WinEvents. Then return rows that have an EventID of 1102. Ensure your Output looks like the output in the \u0027expected result\u0027.",
                                            "dataset":  "Events",
                                            "answer":  "RXZlbnRzCnwgZXh0ZW5kIFdpbkV2ZW50cyA9IHRvZHluYW1pYyhXaW5FdmVudHMpCnwgZXh0ZW5kIEV2ZW50SUQgPSBXaW5FdmVudHMuRXZlbnRJRAp8IHdoZXJlIEV2ZW50SUQgPT0gIjExMDIi"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvYXJnLW1heC1hZ2dmdW5jdGlvbgoKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIGFyZ19tYXggb3BlcmF0b3IgZmluZHMgYSByb3cgaW4gYSBncm91cCB0aGF0IG1heGltaXplcyBhIHNwZWNpZmllZCBleHByZXNpc29uIGFuZCByZXR1cm5zIHRoZSB2YWx1ZSBvZiB0aGUgZXhwcmVzc2lvbiB0byByZXR1cm4uPC9icj4KPC9wPgpFeGFtcGxlOiBzdW1tYXJpemUgWyhOYW1lRXhwclRvTWF4aW1pemUgLCBOYW1lRXhwclRvUmV0dXJuIFssIC4uLl0gKT1dIGFyZ19tYXggKEV4cHJUb01heGltaXplLCB8IEV4cHJUb1JldHVybiBbLCAuLi5dKQoKRXhwclRvTWF4aW1pemU6IEV4cHJlc3Npb24gdGhhdCB3aWxsIGJlIHVzZWQgZm9yIGFnZ3JlZ2F0aW9uIGNhbGN1bGF0aW9uLjwvYnI+CkV4cHJUb1JldHVybjogRXhwcmVzc2lvbiB0aGF0IHdpbGwgYmUgdXNlZCBmb3IgcmV0dXJuaW5nIHRoZSB2YWx1ZSB3aGVuIEV4cHJUb01heGltaXplIGlzIG1heGltdW0uIEV4cHJlc3Npb24gdG8gcmV0dXJuIG1heSBiZSBhIHdpbGRjYXJkICgpIHRvIHJldHVybiBhbGwgY29sdW1ucyBvZiB0aGUgaW5wdXQgdGFibGUuIDwvYnI+CjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgYXJnX21heChDb21wdXRlciwgRXZlbnRJRCkgIDwvYnI+CgpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGFyZ19tYXgoVGltZUdlbmVyYXRlZCwgVXNlckRpc3BsYXlOYW1lKSA8L2JyPgo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KYXJnX21heCBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIHJldHVybiB0aGUgaGlnaGVzdCBvciBtb3N0IHJlY2VudCBsb2cgZm9yIGEgc3BlY2lmaWVkIGl0ZW0uIFRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiB1c2UgZm9yIHRoaXMgb3BlcmF0b3IgaXMgdG8gZmluZCB0aGUgbW9zdCByZWNlbnQgbG9nIGluZ2VzdGVkIGZyb20gYSBzb3VyY2UuIFRoaXMgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWZ1bCB3aGVuIHJ1bm5pbmcgY29ubmVjdG9yIGhlYWx0aCBjaGVja3MsIHJlc29ydWNlIHJlcG9ydGluZyBoZWFsdGggY2hlY2tzLCBhbmQgZmluZGluZyBtb3N0IHJlY2VudCBhY3Rpdml0eSBvbiBlbnRpdGllcyBvciBldmVudHMuCjwvcD4K",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Arg_max",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "Arg_maxEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the records from each Location with the most Rain for that Location sorted from most Rain to least",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBhcmdfbWF4KFJhaW4sICopIGJ5IExvY2F0aW9uCnwgc29ydCBieSBSYWluIGRlc2M="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "Arg_maxEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return the amount of Rain and TimeGenerated from each Location with the most Rain for that Location sorted from most Rain to least",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBhcmdfbWF4KFJhaW4sIFJhaW4sIFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQpIGJ5IExvY2F0aW9uCnwgc29ydCBieSBSYWluIGRlc2M="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvYXJnLW1pbi1hZ2dmdW5jdGlvbgoKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIGFyZ19taW4gb3BlcmF0b3IgZmluZHMgYSByb3cgaW4gYSBncm91cCB0aGF0IG1pbmltaXplcyBhIHNwZWNpZmllZCBleHByZXNpc29uIGFuZCByZXR1cm5zIHRoZSB2YWx1ZSBvZiB0aGUgZXhwcmVzc2lvbiB0byByZXR1cm4uIDwvYnI+CkV4YW1wbGU6IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBbKE5hbWVFeHByVG9NaW5pbWl6ZSAsIE5hbWVFeHByVG9SZXR1cm4gWywgLi4uXSApPV0gYXJnX21pbiAoRXhwclRvTWluaW1pemUsIHwgRXhwclRvUmV0dXJuIFssIC4uLl0pCjwvcD4KRXhwclRvTWluaW1pemU6IEV4cHJlc3Npb24gdGhhdCB3aWxsIGJlIHVzZWQgZm9yIGFnZ3JlZ2F0aW9uIGNhbGN1bGF0aW9uLiA8L2JyPgpFeHByVG9SZXR1cm46IEV4cHJlc3Npb24gdGhhdCB3aWxsIGJlIHVzZWQgZm9yIHJldHVybmluZyB0aGUgdmFsdWUgd2hlbiBFeHByVG9NaW5pbWl6ZSBpcyBtaW5pbXVtLiBFeHByZXNzaW9uIHRvIHJldHVybiBtYXkgYmUgYSB3aWxkY2FyZCAoKSB0byByZXR1cm4gYWxsIGNvbHVtbnMgb2YgdGhlIGlucHV0IHRhYmxlLiAKPC9wPgoKICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKgo8cD4KU2VjdXJpdHlFdmVudCB8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBhcmdfbWluKENvbXB1dGVyLCBFdmVudElEKSAgPC9icj4KClNpZ25pbkxvZ3MgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgYXJnX21pbihUaW1lR2VuZXJhdGVkLCBVc2VyRGlzcGxheU5hbWUpIDwvYnI+CjwvcD4KCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqCjxwPgphcmdfbWluIGlzIGJlc3QgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gcmV0dXJuIHRoZSBoaWdoZXN0IG9yIG1vc3QgcmVjZW50IGxvZyBmb3IgYSBzcGVjaWZpZWQgaXRlbS4gVGhlIG1vc3QgY29tbW9uIHVzZSBmb3IgdGhpcyBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB0byBmaW5kIHRoZSBtb3N0IHJlY2VudCBsb2cgaW5nZXN0ZWQgZnJvbSBhIHNvdXJjZS4gVGhpcyBjYW4gYmUgdXNlZnVsIHdoZW4gcnVubmluZyBjb25uZWN0b3IgaGVhbHRoIGNoZWNrcywgcmVzb3J1Y2UgcmVwb3J0aW5nIGhlYWx0aCBjaGVja3MsIGFuZCBmaW5kaW5nIG1vc3QgcmVjZW50IGFjdGl2aXR5IG9uIGVudGl0aWVzIG9yIGV2ZW50cy4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Arg_min",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ArgMinEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the records from each Location with the lowest High temperature for that Location ordered by High from lowest to highest",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBhcmdfbWluKEhpZ2gsICopIGJ5IExvY2F0aW9uCnwgc29ydCBieSBIaWdoIGFzYw=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ArgMinEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return the High and Low temperatures from each Location with the lowest High temperature for that Location ordered by High from lowest to highest",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBhcmdfbWluKEhpZ2gsIExvdykgYnkgTG9jYXRpb24KfCBzb3J0IGJ5IEhpZ2ggYXNj"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9kY291bnQtYWdnZnVuY3Rpb24NCg0KPC9wPg0KDQogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSBkY291bnQgb3BlcmF0b3IgcmV0dXJucyBhbiBlc3RpbWF0ZSBmb3IgdGhlIG51bWJlciBvZiBkaXN0aW5jdCB2YWx1ZXMgdGhhdCBhcmUgdGFrZW4gYnkgYSBzY2FsYXIgZXhwcmVzc2lvbiBpbiBhIHN1bW1hcnkgZ3JvdXAuDQo8L3A+DQoNCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioNCjxwPg0KU2VjdXJpdHlFdmVudCB8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnQoRXZlbnRJRCkgYnkgQ29tcHV0ZXIgIDwvYnI+DQoNClNpZ25pbkxvZ3MgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgZGNvdW50KHRvc3RyaW5nKFN0YXR1cykpIGJ5IFVzZXJEaXNwbGF5TmFtZSkgPC9icj4NCjwvcD4NCg0KICoqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioNCjxwPg0KZGNvdW50IGlzIGJlc3QgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gc3VtbWFyaXplIG9yIGVzdGltYXRlIGhvdyBtYW55IHVuaXF1ZSB2YWx1ZXMgZXhpc3QgZm9yIHNwZWNpZmllZCBpdGVtcy4gVGhpcyBjYW4gYmUgdXNlZnVsIGZvciBydW5uaW5nIGNvbXBhcmlzb25zIHRvIGJhc2VsaW5lcyBvciBrbm93biB2YWx1ZXMgaW4gb3JkZXIgdG8gZGV0ZXJtaW5lIGRldmlhdGlvbnMuIEFuIGV4YW1wbGUgd291bGQgYmUgcnVubmluZyBhIGNvdW50IG9mIHVuaXF1ZSB2YWx1ZXMgZm9yIHVzZXIgbG9naW4gbWV0aG9kcyB0byBzZWUgaWYgYW55IGFjY291bnRzIGFyZSBhdXRoZW50aWNhdGluZyBmcm9tIG1vcmUgdGhhbiBvbmUgc3RhdGUgb3IgY291bnRyeS4gSWYgeWVzLCB0aGlzIG1heSBzaG93IHRoYXQgc29tZXRoaW5nIGFub21hbG91cyBpcyBoYXMgdGFrZW4gcGxhY2UuDQo8L3A+DQo=",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Dcount",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "DcountEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return unique Low temperatures and group the count by location",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBMb3dzID0gZGNvdW50KExvdykgYnkgTG9jYXRpb24="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "DcountEx2",
                                            "question":  "Return the number of distinct locations for each High in Weather sorted from most to least counts and highest to lowest temperatures",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnQoTG9jYXRpb24pIGJ5IEhpZ2gKfCBzb3J0IGJ5IGRjb3VudF9Mb2NhdGlvbiBkZXNjLCBIaWdoIGRlc2M="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCjxwPg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS9kY291bnRpZi1hZ2dmdW5jdGlvbg0KDQo8L3A+DQoNCioqU3VtbWFyeToqKg0KPHA+DQpUaGUgZGNvdW50aWYgb3BlcmF0b3IgcmV0dXJucyBhbiBlc3RpbWF0ZSBvZiB0aGUgbnVtYmVyIG9mIGRpc3RpbmN0IHZhbHVlcyBvZiBleHByZXNzaW9uIG9mIHJvd3MgZm9yIHdoaWNoIHRoZSBib2R5IGV2YWx1YXRlcyB0byB0cnVlLg0KPC9wPg0KDQoqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioNCjxwPg0KU2VjdXJpdHlFdmVudCB8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnRpZihFdmVudElELCB0b3N0cmluZyhFdmVudElEKSBzdGFydHN3aXRoICc0NicpIGJ5IENvbXB1dGVyICA8YnI+DQoNClNpZ25pbkxvZ3MgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgZGNvdW50aWYodG9zdHJpbmcoU3RhdHVzKSwgdG9zdHJpbmcoU3RhdHVzKSBoYXMgJ01GQScpIGJ5IFVzZXJEaXNwbGF5TmFtZSA8YnI+DQo8L3A+DQoNCioqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioNCjxwPg0KZGNvdW50aWYgcGVyZm9ybXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgZnVuY3Rpb25zIGFuZCBwcm92aWRlcyB0aGUgc2FtZSB2YWx1ZSBhcyBkY291bnQgd2hpbGUgcHJvdmlkaW5nIGFkZGl0aW9uYWwgZmlsdGVyaW5nIGFiaWxpdGllcy4gRGNvdW50aWYgaXMgYmVzdCB1c2VkIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBmaW5kIHRoZSBjb3VudCBvZiB1bmlxdWUgdmFsdWVzIHdoaWxlIGFwcGx5aW5nIGZpbHRlcnMuIFVzaW5nIHRoZSBzYW1wbGUgc2NlbmFyaW8gZnJvbSBkY291bnQsIGRjb3VudGlmIHdvdWxkIGFsbG93IGZvciB0aGUgY291bnQgb2YgbG9naW5zIG91dHNpZGUgb2YgdGhlIGV4cGVjdGVkIGxvY2F0aW9uIHRvIGV4Y2x1ZGUgdGhlIGV4cGVjdGVkIHJlc3VsdHMuDQo8L3A+DQo=",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Dcountif",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "DcountifEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the number of distinct locations for each High in Weather if there was Rain that day sorted from most to least counts and highest to lowest temperatures",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHdoZXJlIFJhaW4gPiAwCnwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGRjb3VudChMb2NhdGlvbikgYnkgSGlnaAp8IHNvcnQgYnkgZGNvdW50X0xvY2F0aW9uIGRlc2MsIEhpZ2ggZGVzYw=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvbWF4LWFnZ2Z1bmN0aW9uCgo8L3A+CgogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqCjxwPgpUaGUgbWF4IG9wZXJhdG9yIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIG1heGltdW0gdmFsdWUgYWNyb3NzIGEgZ3JvdXAuCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgbWF4KFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQpICA8L2JyPgpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGRjb3VudGlmKHRvc3RyaW5nKFN0YXR1cyksIHRvc3RyaW5nKFN0YXR1cykgaGFzICdNRkEnKSBieSBVc2VyRGlzcGxheU5hbWUgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgbWF4KGRjb3VudGlmX1N0YXR1cykgPC9icj4KPC9wPgoKICoqV2hlbiB0byB1c2U6KioKPHA+Ck1heCBwZXJmb3JtcyB0aGUgc2FtZSBmdW5jdGlvbmFsaXR5IGFzIGFyZ19tYXguIEl0IGlzIGJlc3QgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgZm9yIHRoZSB0b3AgdmFsdWUgb2YgYSBjb2x1bW4gb3Igd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIGZvciB0aGUgbW9zdCByZWNlbnQgZXZlbnQuCjwvcD4K",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Max",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "MaxEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the hottest High temperature in Weather",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBtYXgoSGlnaCk="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvbWluLWFnZ2Z1bmN0aW9uCgo8L3A+CgogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqCjxwPgpUaGUgbWluIG9wZXJhdG9yIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIG1pbnVtdW0gdmFsdWUgYWNyb3NzIGEgZ3JvdXAuCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgbWluKFRpbWVHZW5lcmF0ZWQpICA8L2JyPgoKU2lnbmluTG9ncyB8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBkY291bnRpZih0b3N0cmluZyhTdGF0dXMpLCB0b3N0cmluZyhTdGF0dXMpIGhhcyAnTUZBJykgYnkgVXNlckRpc3BsYXlOYW1lIHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIG1pbihkY291bnRpZl9TdGF0dXMpIDwvYnI+CjwvcD4KCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqCjxwPgpNaW4gcGVyZm9ybXMgdGhlIHNhbWUgZnVuY3Rpb25hbGl0eSBhcyBhcmdfbWluLiBJdCBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIGZvciB0aGUgbG93ZXN0IHZhbHVlIG9mIGEgY29sdW1uIG9yIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyBmb3IgdGhlIG9sZGVzdCBldmVudC4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Min",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "MinEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return the coldest Low temperature in Weather",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IHN1bW1hcml6ZSBtaW4oTG93KQ=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvbXZleHBhbmRvcGVyYXRvcgoKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIG12LWV4cGFuZCBvcGVyYXRvciBleHBhbmRzIGEgZHluYW1pYyBsaXN0IG9mIGl0ZW1zIGludG8gbXVsdGlwbGUgcmVjb3Jkcy4gVGhlc2UgZHluYW1pYyBsaXN0cyB3aWxsIGFwcGVhciBhcyBuZXN0ZWQgSlNPTiBsaXN0cyB0aGF0IGhhdmUgbm90IGJlZW4gc2VwZXJhdGVkLiBUaGUgcmVzdWx0IG9mIHRoaXMgY2FsbCB3aWxsIHNlcGFyYXRlIHRoZSBpdGVtcyBmcm9tIHRoZSBsc2l0IGludG8gaW5kaXZpZHVhbCByb3dzLgo8L3A+CgogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgZXh0ZW5kIEVudGl0eSA9IHRvZHluYW1pYyhFbnRpdGllcykgfCBtdi1leHBhbmQgRW50aXR5CjwvcD4KCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqCjxwPgpNdi1leHBhbmQgaXMgYmVzdCB1c2VkIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBleHBhbmQgb3IgdW5wYWNrIGEgbmVzdGVkIG9yIHJlZ3VsYXIgSlNPTiBhcnJheS4gVGhpcyBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIHV0aWxpemUgY29udGVudHMgb2YgdGhlIGFycmF5IGZvciBjaGVja3MsIGpvaW5zLCBvciBjYWxsaW5nIG9uIHRoZSBjb250ZW50IGluIG90aGVyIHF1ZXJpZXMuCjwvcD4K",
        "tab":  "Advanced",
        "section":  "Mvexpand",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "MvexpandEx1",
                                            "question":  "Use mvexpand to expand the name column in the \u0027shapes\u0027 table to individual rows.",
                                            "dataset":  "shapes",
                                            "answer":  "c2hhcGVzCnwgbXZleHBhbmQgbmFtZQ=="
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "MvexpandEx2",
                                            "question":  "Use mvexpand to expand `kids` from the `parents` table.",
                                            "dataset":  "parents",
                                            "answer":  "cGFyZW50cwp8IG12LWV4cGFuZCBraWRz"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  2
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvZGF0YXRhYmxlb3BlcmF0b3I/cGl2b3RzPWF6dXJlbW9uaXRvcgoKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIGRhdGF0YWJsZSBvcGVyYXRvciB0YWtlcyBhIGNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24gaW4gYXMgaW5wdXQgYW5kIHJldHVybnMgYSB0YWJsZSBiYXNlZCBvbiB0aGUgY29uZmlndXJhdGlvbi4gVGhlIGNvbmZpZ3VyYXRpb24gY29uc2lzdHMgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIGNvbHVtbiBhbmQgdGhlIGZvcm1hdCBvZiB0aGUgZGF0YSB0aGF0IHRoZSBjb2x1bW4gd2lsbCBjb250YWluLgo8L3A+CgogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpkYXRhdGFibGUgKERhdGU6ZGF0ZXRpbWUsIEV2ZW50OnN0cmluZykgW2RhdGV0aW1lKDE5MTAtMDYtMTEpLCAiQm9ybiIsIGRhdGV0aW1lKDE5MzAtMDEtMDEpLCAiRW50ZXJzIEVjb2xlIE5hdmFsZSIsIGRhdGV0aW1lKDE5NTMtMDEtMDEpLCAiUHVibGlzaGVkIGZpcnN0IGJvb2siLCBkYXRldGltZSgxOTk3LTA2LTI1KSwgIkRpZWQiXQo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KRGF0YXRhYmxlIGlzIGJlc3QgdXNlZCB3aGVuIGxvb2tpbmcgdG8gY29uc3RydWN0IGEgc3RhdGljIHRhYmxlIG9mIGluZm9ybWF0aW9uIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIHVzZWQgdG8gcnVuIGNvbXBhcmlzaW9ucywgY2hlY2tzLCBvciBqb2lucyB3aXRoaW4gYSByZWd1bGFyIGxvZyBiYXNlZCBxdWVyeS4gCjwvcD4K",
        "tab":  "Dataset",
        "section":  "Datatable",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "DatatableEx1",
                                            "question":  "Create a custom datatable of cities with Location of Boston, Chicago, and Portland",
                                            "dataset":  "",
                                            "answer":  "ZGF0YXRhYmxlIChMb2NhdGlvbjpzdHJpbmcpIFsKICAgICJCb3N0b24iLCJDaGljYWdvIiwiUG9ydGxhbmQiCl0="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvbGV0c3RhdGVtZW50Cgo8L3A+CgogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqCjxwPgpUaGUgbGV0IG9wZXJhdG9yIGJpbmRzIG5hbWVzIHRvIGV4cHJlc3Npb25zLiBMZXQgYWxsb3dzIGZvciB1c2VycyB0byBlc3RhYmxpc2ggdmFyaWFibGVzIHdpdGggc3RhdGljIHZhbHVlcyBvciBldmVuIHRha2Ugb24gdGhlIHJlc3VsdHMgb2YgYSBxdWVyeS4gTGV0IGlzIGRlZmluZWQgYmVmb3JlIHRoZSBtYWluIGJvZHkgb2YgdGhlIHF1ZXJ5Lgo8L3A+CgogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpsZXQgSVBBZGRyZXNzZXMgPSBTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgc3VtbWFyaXplIGJ5IElQQWRkcmVzczsgU2VjdXJpdHlBbGVydCB8IHdoZXJlIHRvZHluYW1pYyhFbnRpdGllcykgaW4gSVBBZGRyZXNzZXMKCmxldCBFYXN0VVNEZXZpY2VzID0gZGF0YXRhYmxlKG5hbWU6c3RyaW5nKSBbCiAgICAnZGMwMScsCiAgICAnZGMwMicsCiAgICAnZGMwMycsCiAgICAnZXVzZncnCl07ClNlY3VyaXR5RXZlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBFYXN0VVNEZXZpY2VzIGhhc19hbnkoQ29tcHV0ZXIpCgpsZXQgcXVlcnkxID0gVGFibGUgfCBwcmVkaWNhdGU7CmxldCBxdWVyeTIgPSBUYWJsZSB8IHByZWRpY2F0ZTsKcXVlcnkxCnwgam9pbiBxdWVyeSAyIG9uIENvbW1vbkNvbHVtbgo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KbGV0IGlzIGEgZmFudGFzdGljIHdheSB0byBkZWNsYXJlIGEgbmV3IHZhcmlhYmxlIHRoYXQgY2FuIGJlIGVpdGhlciBzdGF0aWMgb3IgZHluYW1pYy4gQXMgc2hvd24gaW4gdGhlIGV4YW1wbGUgYWJvdmUsIHRoZSB2YXJpYWJsZSBjYW4gdGFrZSBvbiB0aGUgdmFsdWVzIG9mIGFub3RoZXIgcXVlcnkuIFdoZW4gcGVyZm9ybWluZyBqb2lucywgbGV0IGNhbiBiZSBzZXQgdmFyaWFibGVzIHRvIHRha2Ugb24gdGhlIHJlc3VsdHMgZnJvbSB0aGUgMiBxdWVyaWVzIGFuZCB0aGVuIGpvaW4gaW4gYSBtb3JlIHNpbXBsaWZpZWQgd29ya2Zsb3cuIAo8L3A+Cg==",
        "tab":  "Dataset",
        "section":  "Let",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "LetEx1",
                                            "question":  "Create a variable called SeattleLows and set its value to be all cold temperatures for Seattle. Print the value of the variable in descending order.",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer": "IGxldCBTZWF0dGxlTG93cyA9IFdlYXRoZXIgfCB3aGVyZSBMb2NhdGlvbiA9PSAnU2VhdHRsZScgfCBzdW1tYXJpemUgYnkgTG93IHwgb3JkZXIgYnkgTG93IGRlc2M7IFNlYXR0bGVMb3dz"
                                        },
                                        {
                                            "name":  "LetEx2",
                                            "question":  "create two variables called startTime and endTime. Set startTime to be 06/26/2015 and endTime to be 06/27/2015. Return all results for New York City during that time. Note: datetime uses UTC so there may be a 7 hour time difference in the logs generated. If you see results from 06/22, add 7 hours to startTime to remove the extras.",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer": "bGV0IHN0YXJ0VGltZSA9IGRhdGV0aW1lKDA2LzIzLzIwMTUgMDc6MDA6MDApOyBsZXQgZW5kVGltZSA9IGRhdGV0aW1lKDA2LzI1LzIwMTUgMDA6MDA6MDApOyBXZWF0aGVyIHwgd2hlcmUgVGltZUdlbmVyYXRlZCBiZXR3ZWVuKHN0YXJ0VGltZS4uZW5kVGltZSkgfCB3aGVyZSBMb2NhdGlvbiA9PSAnTmV3IFlvcmsgQ2l0eSc="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvZXh0ZW5kb3BlcmF0b3IKCjwvcD4KCiAqKlN1bW1hcnk6KioKPHA+ClRoZSBFeHRlbmQgb3BlcmF0b3IgY3JlYXRlcyBhIHZhcmlhYmxlIGFuZCBjb2x1bW4gd2l0aGluIHRoZSBib2R5IG9mIHRoZSBxdWVyeS4gVGhlIHZhcmlhYmxlIGNyZWF0ZWQgY2FuIHRha2Ugb24gdGhlIHZhbHVlIG9mIGFub3RoZXIgY29sdW1uIG9yIHRha2Ugb24gYSBzdGF0aWMgdmFsdWUuIEV4dGVuZCBpcyBhbHNvIHVzZWQgZm9yIGlmZiwgY2FzZSwgYW5kIG90aGVyIG9wZXJhdG9ycy4KPC9wPgoKICoqRXhhbXBsZToqKgo8cD4KU2VjdXJpdHlBbGVydCB8IGV4dGVuZCBpc1NlbnRpbmVsID0gaWZmKFByb3ZpZGVyTmFtZSBoYXMgJ2FzaScsICdZZXMnLCAnTm8nKSB8IHByb2plY3QgQWxlcnROYW1lLCBpc1NlbnRpbmVsCgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgZXh0ZW5kIEVudGl0eSA9IHRvZHluYW1pYyhFbnRpdGllcykgfCBtdi1leHBhbmQgRW50aXR5Cgo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KRXh0ZW5kIGFsbG93cyBmb3IgdGhlIGNyZWF0aW9uIG9mIHZhcmlhYmxlcyBmcm9tIHdpdGhpbiB0aGUgYm9keSBvZiB0aGUgcXVlcnkuIFZhcmlhYmxlcyBjYW4gdGFrZSBvbiB0aGUgdmFsdWUgb2Ygb3RoZXIgaXRlbXMgd2l0aGluIHRoZSBsb2dzIG9yIGEgc3RhdGljIHZhbHVlIHRoYXQgaXMgZGVpbmZlZCBieSB0aGUgdXNlci4gSXQgaXMgYmVzdCB0byB1c2UgZXh0ZW5kIHdoZW4gbG9va2luZyB0byBjYWxsIHVwb24gdmFyaWFibGVzIG9yIG1hbmlwdWxhdGUgdmFsdWVzIHRoYXQgbmVlZCB0byBiZSByZXRhaW5lZC4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Dataset",
        "section":  "Extend",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ExtendEx1",
                                            "question":  "Add a Range column to Weather that contains the difference between High and Low temperatures",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "V2VhdGhlcgp8IGV4dGVuZCBSYW5nZSA9IEhpZ2gtTG93"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkNCg0KaHR0cHM6Ly9kb2NzLm1pY3Jvc29mdC5jb20vZW4tdXMvYXp1cmUvZGF0YS1leHBsb3Jlci9rdXN0by9xdWVyeS91bmlvbm9wZXJhdG9yP3Bpdm90cz1henVyZW1vbml0b3INCg0KKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqDQo8cD4NClRoZSB1bmlvbiBvcGVyYXRvciB0YWtlcyB0d28gb3IgbW9yZSB0YWJsZXMgYW5kIHJldHVybnMgdGhlIHJvd3Mgb2YgdGhlbSBhbGwgaW4gYSBzdGFja2VkIGZhc2hpb24uDQo8L3A+DQoNCioqRXhhbXBsZToqKg0KPHA+DQpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgdW5pb24gU2VjdXJpdHlJbmNpZGVudA0KT2ZmaWNlQWN0aXZpdHkgfCB1bmlvbiB3b3Jrc3BhY2UoJ3dvcmtzcGFjZW51bWJlcjInKS5PZmZpY2VBY3Rpdml0eQ0KU2Vjcml0eUJhc2VsaW5lIHwgd2hlcmUgQ29tcHV0ZXIgaGFzICdkYzAxJyB8IHVuaW9uIFVwZGF0ZSB3aGVyZSBDb21wdXRlciBoYXMgJ2RjMDEnDQoNCjwvcD4NCg0KKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKg0KPHA+DQpVbmlvbiBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIGNvbWJpbmUgcmVzdWx0cyBmcm9tIHR3byBvciBtb3JlIHRhYmxlcyBpbnRvIG9uZSBsb2NhdGlvbi4gVW5pb24gaXMgYWxzbyB0aGUgbWFpbiBvcGVyYXRvciB3aGVuIHBlcmZvcm1pbmcgY3Jvc3Mtd29ya3NwYWNlIHF1ZXJpZXMuDQo8L3A+",
        "tab":  "Dataset",
        "section":  "Union",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "UnionEx1",
                                            "question":  "Combine these two cities datatables into a single datatable using the union statement\u003cbr/\u003elet cities1 = datatable(Location:string)[\"Boston\",\"Eugene\",\"Houston\"];\u003cbr/\u003elet cities2 = datatable(Location:string)[\"Boise\",\"Chicago\",\"Tampa\"];",
                                            "dataset":  "",
                                            "answer":  "bGV0IGNpdGllczEgPSBkYXRhdGFibGUoTG9jYXRpb246c3RyaW5nKVsiQm9zdG9uIiwiRXVnZW5lIiwiSG91c3RvbiJdOwpsZXQgY2l0aWVzMiA9IGRhdGF0YWJsZShMb2NhdGlvbjpzdHJpbmcpWyJCb2lzZSIsIkNoaWNhZ28iLCJUYW1wYSJdOwpjaXRpZXMxCnwgdW5pb24gY2l0aWVzMg=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+CiBodHRwczovL2RvY3MubWljcm9zb2Z0LmNvbS9henVyZS9kYXRhLWV4cGxvcmVyL2t1c3RvL3F1ZXJ5L2pvaW5vcGVyYXRvcj9waXZvdHM9YXp1cmVtb25pdG9yCgo8L3A+CgogKipTdW1tYXJ5OioqCjxwPgpUaGUgam9pbiBvcGVyYXRvciBtZXJncmVzIHRoZSByb3dzIG9mIHR3byB0YWJsZXMgdG8gZm9ybSBhIG5ldyB0YWJsZSBieSBtYXRjaGluZyB0aGUgc3BlY2lmaWVkIHZhbHVlcy4KClRoZXJlIGFyZSBzZXZlcmFsIHR5cGVzIG9mIGpvaW5zOgoKa2luZD1sZWZ0YW50aSwga2luZD1sZWZ0c2VtaSBUaGUgcmVzdWx0IHRhYmxlIGNvbnRhaW5zIGNvbHVtbnMgZnJvbSB0aGUgbGVmdCBzaWRlIG9ubHkuCgpraW5kPXJpZ2h0YW50aSwga2luZD1yaWdodHNlbWkgVGhlIHJlc3VsdCB0YWJsZSBjb250YWlucyBjb2x1bW5zIGZyb20gdGhlIHJpZ2h0IHNpZGUgb25seS4KCmtpbmQ9aW5uZXJ1bmlxdWUsIGtpbmQ9aW5uZXIsIGtpbmQ9bGVmdG91dGVyLCBraW5kPXJpZ2h0b3V0ZXIsIGtpbmQ9ZnVsbG91dGVyIEEgY29sdW1uIGZvciBldmVyeSBjb2x1bW4gaW4gZWFjaCBvZiB0aGUgdHdvIHRhYmxlcywgaW5jbHVkaW5nIHRoZSBtYXRjaGluZyBrZXlzLiBUaGUgY29sdW1ucyBvZiB0aGUgcmlnaHQgc2lkZSB3aWxsIGJlIGF1dG9tYXRpY2FsbHkgcmVuYW1lZCBpZiB0aGVyZSBhcmUgbmFtZSBjbGFzaGVzLgo8L3A+CgogKipFeGFtcGxlOioqCjxwPgpTaWduaW5Mb2dzIHwgd2hlcmUgVXNlckRpc3BsYXlOYW1lIGhhcyAnam9obmRvQGNvbnRvc28uY29tJyB8IGpvaW4gT2ZmaWNlQWN0aXZpdHkgfCB3aGVyZSBVc2VySWQgaGFzICdqb2huZG9AY29udG9zby5jb20nCgpTZWN1cml0eUFsZXJ0IHwgd2hlcmUgaXNub3RlbXB0eShTeXN0ZW1BbGVydElkKSB8IGV4dGVuZCBBbGVydElkID0gdG9zdHJpbmcoU3lzdGVtQWxlcnRJZCkgfCBqb2luIGtpbmQ9aW5uZXIgKFNlY3VyaXR5SW5jaWRlbnQgfCB3aGVyZSBpc25vdGVtcHR5KEFsZXJ0SWRzKSB8IG12LWV4cGFuZCBBbGVydElkcyB8IGV4dGVuZCBBbGVydElkID0gdG9zdHJpbmcoQWxlcnRJZHMpKSBvbiBBbGVydElkIHwgZXh0ZW5kIGVudGl0eSA9IEVudGl0aWVzIHwgbXYtZXhwYW5kIHRvZHluYW1pYyhbJ2VudGl0eSddKQo8L3A+CgogKipXaGVuIHRvIHVzZToqKgo8cD4KSm9pbiBpcyBiZXN0IHVzZWQgd2hlbiBsb29raW5nIHRvIGpvaW4gY29sdW1ucyBhbmQgZGF0YSBmcm9tIG11bHRpcGxlIHRhYmxlcyB0aGF0IGNhbiBwcm92aWRlIGRlZXBlciBpbnNpZ2h0IGludG8gZXZlbnRzLiBKb2lucyBjYW4gbGVhZCB0byBkZWVwZXIgZGV0ZWN0aW9ucyBhbmQgaHVudGluZyB3aGVuIHB1bGxpbmcgaW4gcmVsZXZhbnQgbG9ncy4KPC9wPgo=",
        "tab":  "Dataset",
        "section":  "Join",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "JoinEx1",
                                            "question":  "Add state data to the Weather table with a left inner join using the following states datatable\u003cbr/\u003elet states = datatable(Location:string,State:string)[\"Houston\",\"TX\",\"Philadelphia\",\"PA\",\"Indianapolis\",\"IN\",\"New York City\",\"NY\",\"Seattle\",\"WA\"];",
                                            "dataset":  "Weather",
                                            "answer":  "bGV0IHN0YXRlcyA9IGRhdGF0YWJsZShMb2NhdGlvbjpzdHJpbmcsU3RhdGU6c3RyaW5nKVsiSG91c3RvbiIsIlRYIiwiUGhpbGFkZWxwaGlhIiwiUEEiLCJJbmRpYW5hcG9saXMiLCJJTiIsIk5ldyBZb3JrIENpdHkiLCJOWSIsIlNlYXR0bGUiLCJXQSJdOwpXZWF0aGVyCnwgam9pbiBzdGF0ZXMgb24gTG9jYXRpb24sICRsZWZ0LkxvY2F0aW9uID09ICRyaWdodC5Mb2NhdGlvbg=="
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    },
    {
        "markdown":  "IVtEb2N1bWVudGF0aW9uXShodHRwczovL3NoaWVsZHMuaW8vYmFkZ2UvLURvY3VtZW50YXRpb24taW5mb3JtYXRpb25hbCkKPHA+Cmh0dHBzOi8vZG9jcy5taWNyb3NvZnQuY29tL2F6dXJlL2RhdGEtZXhwbG9yZXIva3VzdG8vcXVlcnkvZXh0ZXJuYWxkYXRhLW9wZXJhdG9yP3Bpdm90cz1henVyZW1vbml0b3IKPC9wPgoKICoqU3VtbWFyeToqKgo8cD4KVGhlIGV4dGVybmFsZGF0YSBvcGVyYXRvciBhbGxvd3MgZm9yIHF1ZXJpZXMgdG8gcmVmZXJuY2UgZGF0YSB0aGF0IGlzIHN0b3JlZCBvdXRzaWRlIG9mIHRoZSB3b3Jrc3BhY2UuIFRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiB1c2UgY2FzZSBmb3IgdGhpcyBvcGVyYXRvciBpcyB0byBjYWxsIG9uIGRhdGEgdGhhdCBpcyBiZWluZyBzdG9yZWQgd2l0aGluIGFuIEF6dXJlIFN0b3JhZ2UgQWNjb3VudCBibG9iLiBBUEkgZW5kcG9pbnRzIG9yIHdlYnNpdGUgZmlsZXMgY2FuIGFsc28gYmUgY2FsbGVkIGZyb20gd2l0aGluIHRoZSBxdWVyeS4KCkV4dGVybmFsZGF0YSByZXF1aXJlcyB0aGF0IGEgdXNlciB0ZWxscyB0aGUgcXVlcnkgdGhlIHN0cnVjdHVyZSBvZiB0aGUgZGF0YSB0aGF0IHdpbGwgYmUgYnJvdWdodCBpbiBhcyB3ZWxsIGFzIHRoZSBjb2x1bW4gbmFtZXMuIFRoYXQgd291bGQgYXBwZWFyIGFzIHNvOiAoRmlyc3Rjb2x1bW46IGludCwgU2Vjb25kY29sdW1uOiBzdHJpbmcsIFRoaXJkY29sdW1uOiByZWFsKS4gV2hlbiBwdWxsaW5nIGRhdGEgZnJvbSBhIGJsb2IsIGEgU0FTIHRva2VuIHdpbGwgbmVlZCB0byBiZSBnZW5lcmF0ZWQgaW4gb3JkZXIgZm9yIHRoZSBxdWVyeSB0byBhY2Nlc3MgdGhlIGRhdGEuCjwvcD4KCiAqKkV4YW1wbGU6KioKPHA+CmxldCBFeHRlcm5hbFRhYmxlID0gZXh0ZXJuYWxkYXRhKERldmljZTogc3RyaW5nLCBWZXJzaW9uOiByZWFsLCBVc2VyOiBzdHJpbmcpIFtAJ1NUT1JBR0UgQkxPQiBTQVMgVE9LRU4iXSB3aXRoIChmb3JtYXQ9anNvbik7IEV4dGVybmFsVGFibGUKCmxldCBFeHRlcm5hbFRhYmxlID0gZXh0ZXJuYWxkYXRhKERpc3BsYXlOYW1lOnN0cmluZywgVmVyc2lvbjpzdHJpbmcsIEdyb3VwOnN0cmluZykgW0AnaHR0cHM6Ly9zYW1wbGUud2Vic2l0ZS9zYW1wbGVmaWxlLmNzdiddIHdpdGggKGZvcm1hdD1jc3YpOyBFeHRlcm5hbFRhYmxlCjwvcD4KCiAqKldoZW4gdG8gdXNlOioqCjxwPgpFeHRlcm5hbGRhdGEgaXMgYSBjb252ZW5pZW50IHdheSB0byBjYWxsIGRhdGEgZnJvbSBleHRlcm5hbCBzb3VyY2VzIGluIG9yZGVyIHRvIGJlIHVzYWJsZSBpbiBsb2cgZm9ybWF0LiBUaGlzIGFsbG93cyBmb3IgZGF0YSB0byBiZSBzdG9yZWQgZWxzZXdoZXJlIHdoaWxlIHN0aWxsIGJlaW5nIGJyb3VnaHQgaW4gd2l0aG91dCBpbmdlc3Rpb24gY29zdHMuCjwvcD4K",
        "tab":  "External",
        "section":  "ExternalData",
        "exercises":  {
                          "value":  [
                                        {
                                            "name":  "ExternalDataEx1",
                                            "question":  "Return a new datatable based on the following TIC 3.0 mapping CSV\u003cbr/\u003ehttps://raw.githubusercontent.com/Azure/Azure-Sentinel/master/Sample%20Data/Feeds/ZeroTrustTIC3Mapping.csv",
                                            "dataset":  "",
                                            "answer":  "bGV0IEV4dGVybmFsVGFibGUgPSBleHRlcm5hbGRhdGEoUmVjb21tZW5kYXRpb25EaXNwbGF5TmFtZTpzdHJpbmcsIENhcGJpbGl0eTpzdHJpbmcsIEZhbWlseTpzdHJpbmcpCltAJ2h0dHBzOi8vcmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbS90ZWFjaGppbmcvVGVhY2hKaW5nLVdvcmtib29rcy9tYWluL0RhdGFzZXRzL1plcm9UcnVzdFRJQzNNYXBwaW5nLmNzdiddCndpdGggKGZvcm1hdD1jc3YpOwpFeHRlcm5hbFRhYmxl"
                                        }
                                    ],
                          "Count":  1
                      }
    }
]
